<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Ritual Of Fire on Polar Larp</title>
    <link>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Ritual Of Fire on Polar Larp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 10:33:21 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Murumbrian Centurion</title>
      <link>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/morumbrain_centurion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 10:33:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/morumbrain_centurion/</guid>
      <description>Capture the Chosen One: Your mission is simple, capture the Chosen One for The Dark Ones so they may be offered the Blessing of Murumbria. If someone steps between you and your goal, you will strike them down with your terrifying power over Darkness. f you capture the chosen one, you must carry them to the Gate to leave, you cannot rift with anyone else but yourself in this time. If the PCs step aside and don’t impede your hunt for the Chosen One, let them by and say something snarky to thank them for their “obedience” or remind them that they are “wise for respecting such power”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murumbrian Wizard</title>
      <link>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/morumbrain_wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 10:33:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/morumbrain_wizard/</guid>
      <description>Capture the Chosen One: Your mission is simple, capture the Chosen One for The Dark Ones so he may be offered the Blessing of Murumbria. If someone steps between you and your goal, you will strike them down with your terrifying power over Darkness. f you capture the chosen one, you must carry him to the Gate to leave, you cannot rift with anyone else but yourself in this time. If the PCs step aside and don’t impede your hunt for the Chosen One, let them by and say something snarky to thank them for their “obedience” or remind them that they are “wise for respecting such power”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corrupted Bloody Fist High Shaman</title>
      <link>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/corrupted_bloody_fist_shaman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/corrupted_bloody_fist_shaman/</guid>
      <description>You have been corrupted by the Murumbrian invasion of the Ritual of Fire. They have blessed you with non-corporeal Form as you became closer to Darkness. Hunt and fight any non Murumbrian you see, your mind has been overwhelmed with The Dark Ones power and now you fight for Murumbria until the hour is over.
Defensives: Resist Poison x3, Cloak Flame x3, Rip from Binding x3, Will to Live (Racial), Resist Sleep x3, Resist Fear x3, Dodge x3, Phase x3, Bane Death x3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback: Cryptic Wishes</title>
      <link>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/feedback_scott_bennnett/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 10:33:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/feedback_scott_bennnett/</guid>
      <description>In the brief it&amp;rsquo;s a treasure hunter but in the synopsis it&amp;rsquo;s a family crypt which one is it.
How are you planning to kill time while we get the different levels set up. it feels like a bit of time will be needed.
What costuming does the Genie wear?
Give that dwarf that goes into town a real card. Don&amp;rsquo;t make him go into the crypt and get killed. I don&amp;rsquo;t see that happening easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baleful Fire Drake</title>
      <link>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/baleful-fire-drake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/roles/baleful-fire-drake/</guid>
      <description>Special Ability: With a 30 count a Baleful Fire Drake can set a Stonewood build on flame as if it were a normal structure. The Baleful Fire Drake will need to complete a count for each side of the building to fully engulf. Once a building is complete make a bunch of noise and loudly call out “BURNING COUNT COMPLETE X BUILDING IS ON FIRE!”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the ritual to summon the fire drakes</title>
      <link>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/the_ritual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloryforthefist.netlify.app/current_writeups/ritual_of_fire/the_ritual/</guid>
      <description>All the orcs chant in a call and response then each orc pulls a &amp;ldquo;straw&amp;rdquo; from the shamans hand the one who draws the short straw is sacrificed as part of the ritual.
We know that you can help us.
(the crowd answers) Burn burn tear the sky asunder
But we know you extract a heavy roll
(the crowd answers) Burn burn tear the sky asunder
We pay this toll so gladly</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
